[Music]
3 2 1 he's an innovator Visionary he's a
prophet the pro scrimp a product that
uses some of the things that we've
perfected over our
[Music]
[Applause]
years good morning good
morning let's remind ourselves where
this all started 20 years ago we created
our first product the Ali G 3 years
later we introduced our next character
retaining the sexism and stupidity of
Ali we added a mustache and
anti-Semitism to create the
[Applause]
borax after the amazing success of the
Borat we asked you what you would like
to see in our next product you told us
like ability you said subtlety and
heterosexuality we gave you the
Bruno that product was the first ever to
feature a completely bleached
anus but hey what's next well our
Engineers have worked night and day to
bring you something that we're really
proud of we call it the knobby in the
knobby we have built from the ground up
a character with 12% more likability
than even the bull rat and made him 15%
more idiotic than the Ali G move away
from the car soon as I printed your
ticket not that
one oh these heated Saints make you feel
like you've pissed yourself there are no
heated
seats so let's have a look at some of
the unique design features of the kni
firstly we completely shaved his chin
creating an unrestricted mouth able to
deliver
24% more
expletives nobody boogers me brother
ass ass okay ass oh
[Music]
me we also designed an incredible
virtual platform for the knobby to
operating the brothers Grimsby the
brothers Grimsby has a plot 15% thinner
than any of our
competitors it's actually the smallest
and lightest and most confusing plot
that's ever been released from a major
Studio I'm not including pornos this
thinness this slenderness allows a lot
more time for a new feature we've called
destructive mindless violence or as we
call it
DMV will you stop shooting everything
excuse me which way to the stadium down
there and that's not all we've also
managed to do what the NRA have been
doing for over 50 years in America
putting guns in the hands of complete
idiots a with the gun mistaken for
a spy while trying to keep his family
together it just
works but the Innovation doesn't stop
there our team took the sexual depravity
that you guys have grown to love over
the years and we've expanded it to
places that you wouldn't even imagine
were possible I'm hungry for Grimsby
breakfast well the buffet is open I'll
need a table for one so you can eat in
about 60
Minutes the Grimsby
breakfast the brothers Grimsby is our
finest most advanced product yet we
we've grown to love it and we believe
that you will love it too to thank you
and goodbye changing the world you guys
are
amazing